// eslint-disable-next-line camelcase
const Dams_falls_lakes = [
	{
		questionText: 'Largest Dam',
		ans: ['Bhakra Nangal Dam,Sutlej'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Longest Dam',
		ans: ['Hirakud'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Highest Dam',
		ans: ['Tehri Dam'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Tehri Dam',
		ans: ['Bhagirathi,U.K'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Largest Hyderoelectric Dam',
		ans: ['Konya Hydro Electric dam, M.H, konya River'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Oldest Dam',
		ans: ['Bhavani Sagar Dam,T.N'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Naptha Jhakri HydroElectric project',
		ans: ['Sutlej'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Sal Hydroelectric Powerstation',
		ans: ['Chenab'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Chamera Dam',
		ans: ['Ravi River'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Lakhwar MultiPurpose Project',
		ans: ['Yamuna'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Madikhed Dam',
		ans: ['Sindhu'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Dams on Krishna',
		ans: ['Doom (M.H)', 'Almitti-Karnataka', 'Srisailam, nagarjuna'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Dams on Kaveri',
		ans: ['Krishna Raju sagar Dam-k.A', 'Mettur Dam , Upper Anaicut dam - T.N'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Sardar Sarovar Dam',
		ans: ['GT-Narmada'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Omkareswar Dam',
		ans: ['Narmada,mp'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Largest Irrigation Canal',
		ans: ['Indragandi Can,Rajastan'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Largest Irrigation Project',
		ans: ['Kaleswaram Lift Irrigation Project, Telangana'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Indra Sagar Dam',
		ans: ['Narmada, mp'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Dams on River Chamba',
		ans: [
			'Gandhi Sagar Dam, Jawahar Sagar Dam, Rana Pratap sagar dam  -- Rajastan',
		],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Dhuadhar/smokhindra falls',
		ans: ['Narmada'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Kunchikal Falls',
		ans: ['Varahi River, Karnataka', 'Largest falls'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Jog Falls',
		ans: ['Saraswathi,ka'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Rakim Kund falls',
		ans: ['Gayghat River'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Keoti Falls',
		ans: ['Mahan River, mp'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Gokak Falls',
		ans: ['Gataprapha'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Largest Brackish/lagoon',
		ans: ['Chilika Lake'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Largest freshwater Lake',
		ans: ['Wular, J&K'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Only floting lake',
		ans: ['Loktak, manipur'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Dal Lake',
		ans: ['J&K', 'Famous for House boats'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Pongang lake',
		ans: ['Ladhak'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Tsomgo Lake',
		ans: ['Sikkim'],
	},
	{
		questionText: ' Badkhal Lake',
		ans: ['Haryana'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Pichola Lake',
		ans: ['Rajastan'],
	},
];

// eslint-disable-next-line camelcase
export default Dams_falls_lakes;
